- All right. You ready?
- Okay. Yeah.
- Yep.
- Mom and I are gonna win.
- Not a chance.
- Why am I doing this again?
- Fatherly duties.
- Oh, yeah, I remember those.
- Go!
- Go! Go! Come on!
Wait for me.
- Getting into the corners.
- Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
Down the beach.
Yeah. Here we go. Okay, I got it.
Okay.
- I got it.
- All right.
Hey! Come on, Denise.
- Okay. All right.
- That's great, man.
- Hey, man.
- Nice.
- You got a great family.
- Ah.
You're a lucky man.
Yes, I am.
- A little bit more.
- Mm-hmm.
- Two--
- Hey, Mom.
Look who wanted to come out and play.
Sorry, just-- Give me one second.
Brian. No.
You can't leave Starbuck at home.
He loves the summer block party.
Honey, he loves it too much. All right?
Your dad and I both said
you can't bring him.
No.
Dad said it was okay.
Okay.
Starbuck?
Starbuck, listen to me. Right.
You can stay, but you have to be good.
All right? No biting. No digging holes.
And no stealing food.
See? He knows.
So what are you gonna do
after we graduate?
Oh, my mom's gonna help me
get a job at Michigan Bell.
What about you?
I can't afford it.
But if I could, I'd go to Cornell.
That's where Carl Sagan teaches.
Who's Carl Sagan?
You've never heard of Carl Sagan's Cosmos?
No, is that like science fiction?
No, he's an astronomer.
Mmm.
Uh, he wrote that human beings
are like butterflies
who flutter for a day
and think it's forever.
That's kind of depressing, isn't it?
I don't think so.
Katie.
Hey, it's good to see you, babe.
You got here early.
I wanted to spend the day with you.
Aw.
Audrey, look out!
Go!
Good boy. Good boy.
Hey.
These are just about ready.
Oh, I'm sorry I can't do
the grilling. I-I gotta go.
Can't-- Why? You said you'd do it.
Yeah. They need me to do some
deliveries this afternoon.
I thought you were quitting the side jobs
after Chrysler brought you back.
Well, yeah, I just wanna make
a few extra bucks.
What's the big deal?
Well, uh...
We agreed we needed a family day.
And now, you're leaving.
Uh, and we agreed that
Starbuck should stay home.
And then you told Brian
he could bring him.
Yeah, well, just let
the boy hang out with his dog.
Can we talk for a minute?
Mom and Dad are fighting again.
Do you think they're ever gonna get a...
No.
No, they wouldn't do that.
How long are we gonna keep
putting off the conversation?
Oh, can't we just enjoy the weekend?
It's not working.
The kids can feel it.
Brian's already acting out.
He's just being a 13-year-old.
Greg, stop doing that.
- Doing what?
- Ignoring the problem.
It's a beautiful day, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Look, I-- I gotta go.
I-- I'll see you tonight.
Star player
Lance Parrish had two hits
despite the Tigers losing to the Rangers.
And speaking of stars,
NASA is still tracking
a series of unusual ripples in space
coming off an unprecedented wave...
That is so sweet of you.
- ...of solar flares.
- Come on inside.
Due to this activ--
Have you told your husband
about your book?
No.
I don't think he'd appreciate it.
Well, that's a shame.
I love what you've written so far.
Thank you.
It's hard to describe how much
this surprised me.
I would never have guessed
that you could write something so intense.
Well, I mean, it's not really me.
It's-It's just a story.
Well, I love some of the little details.
Like the fact that she always
keeps her yellow suitcase packed.
Ready to leave for New York
the minute she gets up the nerve to do it.
And that scene
where she's holding
the suitcase in her arms,
and cries while she watches her children
playing in the yard
is heartbreaking and beautifully written.
Thank you.
I'd like to read the next
draft when you're finished.
Are you sure? You have been
so generous with your time.
I-I feel bad.
Denise, I edited my husband's
work for 40 years
without a lot of gratitude.
I'm more than happy
to give some editorial advice
to someone who cares.
Well, thank you so much.
I-I can't tell you
how much I appreciate it.
Oh. Do you have a minute?
Sure.
I-I want to show you something
in the backyard.
Strange, isn't it?
Yeah.
What do you think it is?
I don't know.
I can get a botany book from the library
and maybe we can figure it out.
I just don't know how
it could've grown so fast.
I'm certain it wasn't here
a couple days ago.
It grew this much in two days?
Well, either that or somebody
transplanted it as a joke.
I don't know how funny that is.
Want me to pull it up for you?
Sure, if you don't mind.
Hey, let me get some of that flask, bro.
Just a sip. You're being greedy.
Have you told your parents yet?
No.
Aren't you a little bit worried about it?
A little bit.
Maybe they just, like,
won't find out about it.
Of course they will.
Charles Tucker's older brother's
gonna beat the hell out of you.
You broke the kid's arm, Brian.
Of course he's not gonna forget.
- It was an accident.
- Bullshit.
You threw a stick
into the spokes of his tires.
What'd you think would happen?
Thought he'd go flying
off his bike like Superman.
Oh, he did.
Way up into the air.
Yeah, you're lucky he's not dead.
I mean, when his brother sees
you, he's going to kill you.
And I mean kill you.
That's why I got my bow and arrow.
What good is that gonna do?
Put an arrow in him.
Hey. Hey.
Take a look.
That's the new girl, right?
Oh, get down.
Yeah.
Should be nice.
Oh, she's pretty.
Heard she goes
to some kinda private school.
She doesn't look rich.
You don't have to be rich
to go to private school.
You just gotta be, like,
Catholic or something.
I'm thinking of becoming Catholic.
Shut up, Fergus. Idiot.
Denise!
Hey, Denise!
Mel, what is it?
Your dog got in my yard again last night.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Oh, you're sorry? Okay, well,
I woke up hearing the damn thing barking.
He would not shut up.
Do you know I barely slept last night?
Brian said there's some raccoons
in the trees back there.
Starbuck must be trying to...
You don't understand. I don't
care why he's doing it.
Okay, he's now dug a hole under my fence.
He has shit all over my yard.
I am just so sick of it.
I-- Well, I'll make sure
that he is on a leash
until we get the hole filled, okay?
Fine. Fine. But you know what?
If that dog comes in my yard
one more time,
I'm gonna shoot it.
Listen, Mel. My husband
is too kind to say this,
but if you so much as point a gun
in the direction of my dog,
I'll burn your damn house down.
- See you tomorrow.
- See you later, man.
Hey, Brian.
You help me with this?
Yeah, Dad.
Is everything okay?
Yeah.
I made some good tips.
I got us a pizza for dinner.
Great. I'm starving.
Well, there's plenty to eat.
Why do we gotta take this thing off?
Wouldn't it just be easier
to leave it on all the time?
Yeah, it embarrasses your mother.
Oh.
You're gonna stop
with the cigarettes, right?
I don't smoke.
- Don't lie to me, Brian.
- I'm not.
I can smell it on you.
Sorry, Dad.
- What's with you anyway?
- Nothing.
Trying to impress somebody?
No.
That crap is the reason
your grandpa got his vocal cords cut out.
You don't want cancer, do you?
Uh-uh.
All right. Let's put this
stupid thing in the garage
where your mother can't see it.
I was like, "Hold on."
What was that?
I have no idea.
Mel's really getting to be a problem.
He threatened the dog today.
Wait, what? He better not hurt Starbuck.
No, no, no. Nobody's gonna hurt the dog.
Hey, Starbuck.
This is Mel's head.
You want to bite it, right?
No, no, that's not his head.
That's his balls.
Yeah, Starbuck.
- Here's Mel's testicles.
- Good boy. Get his--
Oh. Okay. Good boy. You want to go get it?
- Come on, get his balls.
- Go get him!
Yay!
He's chomping on them.
That's what he's gonna do to Mel's balls.
Dad, tell Brian to keep his
mouth shut while he's eating.
It's so gross.
Don't talk when you've got
food in your mouth, Brian.
Ew.
- Mom, he's been so gross...
- Mm-hmm.
...since the time he was a little boy.
Do you remember
when he pooped in the bath?
Okay, that was a little poop.
No. No, it wasn't.
No, she's right.
It was a lot of poop.
Okay... so what? What?
I was just like four years old
or something.
Uh-uh.
Now were you or were you not
on the night of June the 13th
in Mrs. Throttlebottom's chicken coop?
Soitenly not! I was in the house!
- What house?
- The doghouse.
Nyuk, nyuk, nyuk, nyuk!
Hey, boy. You're all wet.
Good boy.
What did you see?
Did anybody else
see that weird light
in the backyard last night?
- What weird light?
- The Chicago White Sox...
I don't know where it came from,
but Starbuck was all
freaked out and barking.
Oh, great. That's all we need.
What did it look like?
Well, there was a light coming
through the window.
It was really bright. It flickered.
And then the wind was blowing all crazy.
And then it was gone.
Could have been lights from a helicopter.
Or a UFO.
Aliens.
Shut up, Dad.
How long was he barking for?
Long enough to wake me up.
Hey, Mel, what's going on?
Nothing good.
Kids pulled off one hell
of a prank last night.
What happened?
They didn't do anything to you.
Oh, you gotta see it.
It's gonna take me all day to clean up.
Hey, Mel, what--
what are you talking about?
No, no, come on. Come take a look, Greg.
All right.
Holy shit.
Yes, yes, that is exactly what that is.
That is about a couple
hundred pounds of cow manure.
You think my kids did this?
Either them...
Or your wife.
Oh, come on now, Mel. Really?
- You see, I knew it.
- Hey. Brian. Audrey.
- I knew they did it. Damn it.
- Stop laughing.
I knew it.
Look, they just think it's funny
because it's, uh...
I promise you, my family
had nothing to do with this.
Greg, please. Okay.
If it wasn't them,
then who else did this, huh?
You're the only neighbors
I'm having trouble with.
I have no idea.
But if you need help cleaning
it up, then I'll be here.
And Brian can help, too.
What?
- Thank you, Greg.
- Come on, man.
- I appreciate it.
- All right.
Denise, it's so nice to see you.
Good to see you, Mrs. Valcourt.
I was wondering if you could
help me out with something.
Oh. Yes, what do you need?
Mrs. Huddleston found
this plant in her backyard,
and we're trying to figure out what it is.
Now, I looked through all of these books,
but I can't find anything like it.
Do you have any idea what it could be?
It's funny. It looks a lot
like Pleuromeia.
Uh, Pleuro... What's that?
It can't be Pleuromeia,
because that species has been extinct
for over 200 million years.
- 200 million years?
- Yes.
I'll tell Mrs. Huddleston.
She'll get a kick out of that.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you more.
Hmm.
I like your new bike.
Thanks. I mean, the handlebars
are pretty cool.
I customized them a few days ago.
My bike is all black.
I need a new one.
Yeah, this one's, like, red,
and blue. It's pretty cool.
You think maybe I should get it, too?
I think you'll like it.
Wait! Brian!
It's Kaden Tucker!
- Oh, shit!
- Go, go, go, go!
Brian Platt! Get back here!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
You're dead!
Come on! Let's get him!
- Get him!
- Let's go!
Oh, shit!
Where are you, Brian?
No point in hiding.
Come here, Brian!
Come out, bitchsqueak!
You broke my brother's arm!
Just you wait till we find you, Platt!
Brian!
We're coming for you, Brian!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
You're done, Platt!
Let's go left. We'll find him.
Thank you.
You're welcome. Thanks. Good night.
Right next to his hand.
Let's drink it.
Yeah, let's get drunk.
Man, you can't get drunk
on one can of beer.
Mom!
Dad!
The power's out again.
What was that noise?
It felt like my eardrums popped.
Denise? Kids?
Could have been lightning
striking a transformer.
I don't know.
The clock's dead.
Must have happened just past 11.
- Everybody all right?
- Yeah, Dad, we're fine.
Did you guys see that lightning?
Yeah, it was bright as hell.
The whole sky lit up just like that.
- Where's Mom at?
- I don't know.
Denise, you downstairs?
Yes.
I'm here.
Everybody okay?
Yeah, we're all fine.
Just a little startled, I guess.
What were you doing in the basement?
Huh? Laundry.
Washing your dirty underpants.
Funny, Mom.
My ears are popping like
I just flew in an airplane.
Yeah, mine too.
That doesn't make sense.
What would cause
that type of pressure change?
Yeah, it looks like
the whole neighborhood's lost power.
Phone lines are down.
- Shit.
- Watch your language, Audrey.
Mom, I'm hungry.
Can I get something to eat?
Huh? Yeah.
- Only from the cupboard.
- Okay.
Nobody's opening the fridge
until the power comes back on.
I don't want all that food to go bad.
Did anyone else notice?
The rain stopped.
There's no more thunder.
Yeah, it's quiet.
I think we should all
try and get some sleep,
and hopefully by the time we wake up,
the power will be back on.
- The hell was that?
- Shh.
- Quiet.
- Someone's hurt.
Brian, give me your flashlight.
Wait, no, no, no, Dad.
- Greg.
- What?
I don't think you should go out there.
Well, someone might need help.
Just stay inside, please.
Hello?
Brian, make sure the back door is locked.
- And-And check on the dog.
- Check on the dog.
- Dad, what is happening?
- I don't know.
I think we should stay inside
the house until morning.
There could be power lines down.
I don't know how dangerous
it is out there.
What about the people who were screaming?
Don't they need help?
I don't know who those people are,
but the police will be there to help them.
Back door is locked.
Starbuck's in his doghouse.
- What about the police?
- Thank you, buddy.
Shouldn't we be hearing sirens?
Audrey, stop it. Are you
trying to scare your brother?
No, I'm not. I'm just trying to figure out
what's happening.
Why don't you get some pillows
and blankets,
and we'll all sleep in the family room.
- That's a good idea.
- All together.
Good idea.
Come on. Go get your stuff.
Just a regular slumber party.
Okay, I... [stutters] ...I'll get some snacks.
- I'll get the blankets.
- Yeah.
Still no power?
Nope.
Sucks.
I wanna watch MTV.
We'll get it on soon.
Why is it so warm in here?
I'll open some windows.
- Greg?
- Yeah?
Starbuck got out again.
- How?
- I don't know.
He must have broken his leash
and dug under the fence.
Can I go looking for him?
No, no, not just yet.
I told you there could be power lines down
in the street.
Dad, I'm not stupid.
I'm not gonna grab onto one.
Hey, should we drink the milk
before it goes bad?
Mm-hmm.
Everybody want cereal?
- Yes, please.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Thank you.
You staying home today?
No. No, I can go in a little late.
I'll tell them about the power.
- They'll understand.
- Okay.
I'll go find Starbuck.
And see what kind of damage
the storm caused.
I just hope Mel didn't
do anything to him.
No, no.
He's probably
in the MacAllisters' backyard
trying to get fresh with
that pretty little dachshund.
- Gross, Dad.
- What?
Why don't we go together?
I wanna check on Mrs. Huddleston,
make sure she's okay.
Yeah. All right, let's do that.
You two, stay inside
until your mom and I get back.
- Sure.
- Mm-hmm.
Brian,
Kaden Tucker came by yesterday.
He was looking for you.
Don't tell him I'm here.
Damn it.
Water's not working.
Oh, the main line must have burst.
That was one hell of a storm.
Are there any utilities left to break?
No, we got 'em all.
Good.
Lock the door behind us, okay?
Yeah, Mom.
Oof.
It's hot.
Yeah.
Starbuck!
Do you hear that?
Yeah.
That explains the water being out.
No, I don't think so.
That's not a burst pipe.
That water is steaming hot.
I'm gonna cut through the yards,
head over to the next block,
see if they have power.
I have a feeling that Starbuck's
in the MacAllisters' backyard.
Okay.
Meet you back at the house.
Starbuck!
Mrs. Huddleston?
Hello?
What the hell?
Brian!
Brian! Come here, quick!
Starbuck!
Mrs. Huddleston?
Mrs...
Oh, God, Mrs. Huddleston.
Mrs. Huddleston.
Holy Jesus.
Oh, God.
Brian! Brian, get up here!
What's going on? Why are you yelling?
- I saw something. It was big.
- What'd you see?
And it looked like it was
moving in this direction.
- What was it, an animal?
- I don't know.
Did an elephant escape from the zoo?
It wasn't a damn elephant!
Are you sure you saw something?
- Stop it, Brian! I did.
- Okay, okay,
but you're freaking me out.
Starbuck?
- Come on! Let's go!
- What?
Let's go!
Oh, my God! He's gaining!
Run, Denise!
What the hell's going on?
- No! No!
- Get inside now!
- Get inside!
- I just heard a gunshot.
I can do it.
♪ Flintstones
Meet the Flintstones ♪
- Mom, you put her in?
- Yeah, I got it.
♪They're the modern
Stone-age family ♪
Keep moving. Keep going.
♪ When you're
With the Flintstones ♪
♪ Have a
Yabba-dabba-doo time ♪
Audrey, open the door!
- Brian!
- Okay.
- Audrey, come on!
- Open the door!
Audrey!
Mom, look!
Brian!
Oh, God!
Brian! Audrey! Open the door!
Oh, my God. What is that?
Open the door, quick!
Oh, my God! Quick!
Brian!
- Go!
- Shit.
What is that? What is that?
Mom! Mom.
Mom!
Dad. Dad.
Oh, my God.
I think-- I think-- I think they're gone.
What's happening?
- I don't know.
- What was at the door?
- Dad, what was that?
- We've got to get out of here.
- Why don't we get in the car?
- Yeah.
Go to my parents' house.
Maybe this isn't happening in Chicago.
- That's a good idea.
- Dad, are we gonna die?
No, no, no!
Nobody's gonna die.
- We're all gonna be okay.
- Everybody get some things.
- We're getting out of here.
- Okay.
Go. Come on. Get some things.
Okay.
Audrey, Brian, keep your heads down.
Don't look out the windows.
What about Starbuck?
Are we just leaving him?
He'll be all right.
We can't go looking for him right now.
He'll be here when we get back.
Oh, God.
Shit.
Why are we stopping?
What's happening?
We're gonna go to Gladwin Street.
There's got to be a way out of here.
This is insane.
Where the hell are we?
It's okay.
Mom.
Dad.
What's gonna happen to us?
- Got it?
- Yeah.
You kind of smell like whiskey.
Have you been...
Oh, yeah.
I might have had a little sip.
I guess I needed to calm down.
You can smell it?
Uh-huh.
I wish you wouldn't drink.
Not now.
I need you here with me.
Well, this is a lot to deal with.
Greg, it started before we got here.
Will you please be honest with me?
I, uh...
I was laid off a few weeks ago.
I've been trying to find work,
doing part-time jobs for cash.
Why didn't you tell me?
- Well...
- Mom,
where'd you put the other hammer?
Could you just give us a minute, Brian?
I didn't want you to worry.
Well, that's just stupid.
No, it's not. I--
I need you to remember something.
I can handle anything
you can handle, maybe more.
Brian, find that other hammer?
- No.
- It's in the garage.
It has a yellow handle.
Oh, Audrey, will you start bringing
the supplies down to the basement?
- Everything?
- Yeah, yeah.
We're gonna sleep down there.
It's the safest part of the house.
Okay.
Dad?
What are we gonna do about Starbuck?
Oh, buddy.
I don't think we can do
anything right now.
But Starbuck is a very smart dog.
He'll be okay.
You know he loves you so much.
He'll find his way home.
He will.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
The basement is totally flooded.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
We'll just have to use
the second floor, I guess.
Damn it.
Mom. What is it?
Nothing.
- Please tell me.
- I had--
I had something very important down there.
- What? What? What was it?
- It doesn't matter.
Let's just keep this door closed
and hope the water doesn't get
any higher, all right?
Okay. I'm sorry, Mom.
Thank you.
This is the last of the milk.
Well, we might as well finish it.
Never gonna have milk again.
Don't talk like that.
Maybe dinosaurs have milk.
Don't be stupid.
I can't find any radio stations.
Well, thanks for checking, buddy.
Mom?
Is this the end of the world?
No.
It's not.
What is it then?
I think that our neighborhood,
our whole street...
has moved.
I think...
our house is somewhere else now.
Where?
We're in the past.
Aren't we?
How the hell is that even possible?
I don't know.
It was the lights.
What?
The lights that Starbuck was barking at.
The lights brought us here.
Yeah, maybe.
I mean, Sagan wrote about wormholes.
The lights could be portals
moving things between
different points in time.
Like the plant at Mrs. Huddleston's?
Or the shit in Mel's backyard.
Maybe the lights carried those things
from the past to the present.
And us back to the past.
How?
Well...
the portals could have acted as tremors.
It's like barely noticeable at first.
Swapping small sections of land
between different points in time.
And maybe the tremors grew
until the big one finally hit,
and our whole neighborhood
got swapped out.
Well, if that's true,
then it could take us back home again.
So, what? Are we just gonna wait here?
- Greg.
- Yeah.
Yeah. We're gonna survive.
And we're gonna wait for
the lights to take us back.
That's the plan.
Dad, how do you know
that that's even gonna happen?
We don't know.
Well, I believe it will.
How?
I know.
Because...
God's not gonna let us die here.
Greg,
you only go to church at Christmas,
and now you're telling the kids
- God is looking out for us.
- What about the people...
- You're being ridiculous.
- ...getting eaten by animals?
I believe Dad.
Okay.
Good.
If it makes you feel better, believe him.
I'm just scared.
And I don't want to lie to you.
♪ So wild, standing there ♪
♪ With her hands in her hair ♪
- ♪ I can't help remember ♪
- ♪ ...help remember ♪
- ♪ Just where she touched me ♪
- ♪ There is still no face ♪
♪ Here in her place ♪
♪ So cool ♪
- ♪ ...she was like ♪
- ♪ Jazz on a summer's day ♪
- ♪ Music, high and sweet ♪
- ♪ Then she just blew away ♪
♪ Now she can't be that warm ♪
♪ With the wind ♪
- ♪ In her arms ♪
- ♪ Valerie, call on me ♪
- ♪ Call on me, Valerie ♪
♪ Come and see me ♪
♪ I'm the same boy
I used to be ♪
I know you were
trying to comfort the kids,
but we might be here forever.
You know that, right?
Well, I don't want to believe that.
Of course not, but...
We can't stay in the house indefinitely.
Eventually, we're gonna need
more food, and water--
We would be killed and eaten
if we go outside.
- Is that what you want?
- There are other people here.
Other families are trying to survive.
The smart ones are gonna gather supplies.
Water, food, guns, ammunition.
Well, why don't we wait a few
days and see what happens?
Okay, we can. We can.
- Oh, God.
- What is that?
Mom.
It's okay.
- What's going on?
- It's okay.
Down, down, down.
Get down. Get down. Stay down.
- Are you kidding?
- Are you okay?
This is my house!
Oh, my-- Oh, my God. It's Mel.
He's on his roof.
He's got a gun.
- He's shooting at the dinosaurs?
- Yeah!
Maybe that's a good thing.
He'll scare 'em away.
- Or draw their attention!
- He's a damned idiot.
I see you!
I'm gonna send you back to extinction!
- Oh, no! Get out of the room!
- Go! Go! Get out!
- Kids, please!
- Okay. Okay.
This is my house,
you sons of bitches!
This is my house.
This is my goddamn house.
Ah!
Oh! Ah!
Get off!
- No, no.
- No, no, no. Get off me!
- No.
- Somebody help me!
Help me!
Greg?
- Yeah?
- What are we gonna do?
We can't live like this.
There's got to be some way out of here.
We just all have to stay together, and--
How do you know that?
What? Well, I don't know for
sure. It's just what I feel.
Will you stop being so damn optimistic?
This is not gonna be okay.
Well, what the hell do you want me to do?
I want you to be honest about
the situation. I want you...
That we're stuck here
for the rest of our lives.
That-- That-- That-- That--
That we need to be honest with our kids
- about what that means.
- Everything I do is wrong.
All year, I've been trying
to keep this family together,
and all you've wanted to do
is tear it apart.
How can you say that?
You never want to talk about anything
or deal with anything.
And you have been drinking
and lying about your job.
How is that keeping the family
together, Greg?
- I'm not the only one.
- How did I lie?
All that typing in the basement!
I read your book, Denise!
You wanted to leave us for
a long time, me and the kids.
That's-- No, that is not true!
- Oh, no?
- No, it's just a story!
Oh, bullshit. It reads
exactly like our life!
No. You don't understand!
- You don't understand!
- Oh, is this too much for you?
Is this too much? You can't handle it?
How do you think I feel? How
do you think the kids feel?
- When did you stop loving us?
- Don't say that!
You don't listen to me!
You don't actually hear me!
You don't listen to the words that come...
- Starbuck!
- I'm just here.
No, no, no, no! Starbuck!
...making your whole life happen.
You don't actually hear me!
You nearly...
And you think, "What does 'the me' want?
How is 'the me'..."
I'm the only person
that I think about?
That's what you're supposed to say!
Brian!
Starbuck!
Audrey?
Audrey!
Brian?
Greg! Greg!
Where do you think they went?
I don't know. I don't know.
We'll find them. We'll find them.
I can't believe they'd do this.
Brian!
Audrey!
Starbuck!
Shit.
Brian!
Kids!
Audrey!
What is that?
What do I do?
Just keep going. They'll get out the way.
They're not moving.
Oh, God.
Maybe I could just drive around them?
Tap the horn.
What, we tell every animal
in the neighborhood
- that we're here?
- All right. Well,
drive up on the grass.
- Greg!
- Reverse! Reverse! Go back!
- Oh, my God. No, no, no.
- Oh, my God! Go!
Greg!
- Okay then-- Go, go, go!
- Oh, my God.
No! Come on! Come on!
Greg.
- Greg!
- Oh, it's coming again!
Oh, my God!
Oh, Denise.
Oh, God.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
Greg, go! Go! Go!
Go!
Starbuck!
Starbuck?
You thought it was funny
when you hurt my brother?
No! No!
Ow!
When you broke his arm?
- Stop! Stop it!
- I'm sorry, okay?
Stop! You're gonna kill him!
- Stop!
- He broke your arm!
I didn't mean to.
So what? Who cares?
It doesn't matter anymore!
Please!
- I wanna kill him!
- Leave him alone!
Stop! Get off him!
Please, leave him alone!
Please! Leave him alone!
Please!
I'm sorry.
Oh, God. I'm so sorry.
I don't know what I'm doing.
I don't know what's gonna happen to us.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's just try to find Mom.
Let's go, please! Let's go!
Oh, shit.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go.
Okay. Come on.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Oh, your face looks like
a pepperoni pizza.
Leave me alone.
I don't want to talk about it.
Why did you run away?
I saw Starbuck.
He was by the house, but he's gone now.
Where is he?
I don't know. I can't find him.
Oh, Brian.
You know, he-- he might be...
Don't say it.
- Come on. Come on.
- Somebody help me!
Somebody help me, please!
Hey!
Stay away from her!
- Get away from her!
- Hey!
Over here! Hey!
Help me, please! Please!
Hey.
Where are you going?
Wait.
Come back!
Leave me alone!
We're not gonna hurt you.
Are you okay?
No.
Are you alone?
Your parents?
I'm sorry.
What's your name?
Jeannette.
Okay, okay, I'm Audrey.
And that's my brother, Brian.
Hi.
You can come with us.
We'll find somewhere safe.
Okay?
Thank you.
Brian!
Audrey!
Don't worry, Denise. We'll find them.
They'll be okay.
Go. Go. Go.
What is it?
I think it's the light
that Brian told us about.
Maybe this'll take us back home.
Back to our time.
We need to find the kids
and get back here as quick as we can.
- You should go through it now.
- What are you talking about?
I'll find the kids, and we'll
meet you on the other side.
We go through together or not at all.
I just want you to be safe.
I'm not getting separated
from you and the kids.
Whose house is this?
I don't know, but I did find
some mercurochrome
and some bandages.
Jeannette?
What was it like going to private school?
I never went to public school,
so I don't know how different it is.
We don't pray at our school.
Yeah, you can pray wherever you want.
Nobody has to know.
I guess that's true.
Audrey, do you believe in God?
Not really.
I do.
Yeah,
sometimes I don't either.
Ah.
Does it hurt?
Yeah, a little bit.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
We gotta get home soon.
Mom and Dad are gonna be so worried.
Wait.
Somebody's out there.
Brian?
Audrey?
Mom!
Dad!
Oh, sweetie!
- Oh, we love you so much.
- Oh!
- So much.
- I'm so sorry, Mom.
- No, no, no, no. I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- So happy you're still alive!
- That's okay.
- Come! Come!
- Come here.
- Dad! Dad.
- Son.
Oh, Brian.
Love you guys.
Mom. Dad.
This is Jeannette.
Hello.
Oh, hi, Jeannette.
She's all by herself.
She really needs someone to stay with.
- Well, she can stay with us.
- Yeah, of course she can.
- Take care of you.
- Thank you.
Oh, God.
Greg, we have to go
that way to get home.
I know.
I want you kids to get back in that house
and wait for us.
We're gonna make sure it's safe, okay?
- Okay, come on.
- Yeah. Hurry.
- Are you sure?
- Run, run, run.
Holy shit, they're doing it.
How is this funny?
I... I mean, it's...
Look at his...
You are silly.
I want to take a picture of you.
What?
Picture of you in front of them.
Denise, have you any idea
how much danger we're in?
Please just pose for my photo.
I want to remember
this insane, stupid moment.
Okay, hurry.
Take your crazy photo.
- Smile.
- Cheese.
- Can we go now?
- Yes.
Come on.
Maybe we should cut
through the Samuelsons' yard.
It might be faster.
No, this way is better.
Listen to your father.
Look at that.
Where'd the fire come from?
- Did we start that?
- Maybe.
We gotta get out of here.
Maybe we can find
another one of those portals.
Where do we even look? It all
seems so random, doesn't it?
Yeah.
When it gets dark, we need to
get up someplace high.
Look for the light.
Okay, I'm just trying to think
of someplace high.
Mom! Dad!
- Run!
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Shit.
Help!
No!
Help! Mom! Dad! Help!
Brian!
Over here!
Come on! Hurry!
Hey! Hey! Get away from them!
Denise!
Get out of there! Run!
- Mom! Mom!
Get back!
- Denise!
- Greg!
- Are you okay, baby?
Are you okay?
Greg!
No!
No! Oh, God!
No. No. No.
Don't look. Don't look. Don't look.
Don't look. Don't look.
Don't look.
Mom.
The fire.
What are we gonna do?
Everything's gonna burn down.
It's gonna reach the house.
I'm gonna-- I'm--
Go home and figure it out.
How do you know the house
isn't gonna catch on fire?
Could you just be quiet for one second?
Just get off my back!
Did you see what that thing
just did to your father?
Mom!
Yes.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Kids!
Brian!
Help!
Mom! Help!
Brian!
Brian! No!
No!
Brian!
No! Run!
Are you okay?
Brian! Brian!
Mom?
Where are we gonna go?
We're gonna find somewhere safe.
There isn't anywhere.
Did you see that?
What? What? What is it?
There.
Top of the hill.
That's the same light
Starbuck was barking at.
Your father and I
saw it last night.
I think it might be a way home.
Really?
Grab anything you can use as a weapon.
We're gonna try and get out of here.
Okay.
There it is.
Isn't that Mrs. Valcourt's house?
The librarian?
Yeah.
We're gonna have to go through
the house to get up there.
Okay. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
We're gonna need to time
our jumps to get through it.
Do you want me to go first?
- What?
- We can't go together?
I think it's safer if we go one at a time.
It's hard to know where...
Mom, we don't even know
what's gonna happen to us.
Audrey, I'm just trying to figure out
the least scary way to handle
this for you kids, okay?
Mom, I want to go first.
- You want to go first?
- No, no, no.
It's gonna be your sister or me, okay?
Please, please. I know I can.
I'll see you over there.
What? No, no, no. Jeannette!
Oh, my God! Holy shit!
- Mom, can you see her?
- Oh, my--
- I don't see anything.
- Okay, okay.
Do you guys want to go next?
- Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
Make sure you count it out.
- I know.
- Okay. Okay.
I love you, Brian.
- Love you.
- It's okay.
It's okay. We're gonna be
right behind you.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
...four, five, six, seven, eight.
One, two...
No!
My leg!
Hey! Hey!
Mom! Help me!
Starbuck!
- Starbuck!
- Brian!
- Get away from him!
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Can you walk? Get up.
- It hurts. It hurts.
- Come on. Please.
Come on. Let's go.
- Mom, it hurts!
- I know.
Oh, my God.
It's okay. We're almost there.
Come on.
Mom! Mom!
Oh, my God.
- Get up. Get up, baby.
- Come. Come.
- Come on.
- All right.
Come on. Quick.
Stay behind me! Get behind me!
Mom! Mom!
Mom.
Oh, my God.
Come on. Come on.
Mom!
Mom, where are we gonna go?
Okay.
When they come after me,
I want you to get up there and jump.
- Mom, no! No! No! No!
- No!
No, you can't let them get you!
- No! Please! No!
- I'm so sorry. I love you.
Mom, no! No!
- No!
- I love you!
- No! No!
- They'll get you! No!
Please!
Get away from them!
We're gonna jump together.
- Okay.
No!
How badly are they broken?
- Albert, you have to come.
- Hmm?
Audrey! Brian!
- Mom! Mom!
- Are you okay? Are you okay?
- Yes. Yes!
Are you okay?
What the hell are you doing in my pool?
- I'm sorry!
- Get out of there!
Can you tell us where we are?
What? You're in my backyard.
What year is it?
What kind of question is that?
It's 1982, obviously.
Are there any dinosaurs here?
- What?
- Have you seen any dinosaurs?
Get out of my yard.
Y'all crazy.
Come on.
Mom.
- Does that mean we're safe?
- We're safe?
Yeah.
- We're safe! We're safe.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
We're safe.
I love you, Starbuck.
Wait, where's Jeannette?
- Jeannette?
- I don't think she's here.
We'll find her.
Where the hell is she?
Jeannette?
Audrey!
Jeannette!
You made it!
Follow me. You gotta see this.
Is that?
Yeah.
It's our neighborhood.
It's like nothing happened.
Wait a minute.
Mom, it's July 11th.
This is the night it happened.
What time is it?
There. 10:45.
10:45.
The portal happened at 11:05.
We only have 20 minutes.
I have to find my parents.
- Jeannette. No!
- No, wait! Jeannette!
- I'll bring them up here.
- Let her go.
- I can make it.
- Do not follow--
- Mom, please.
- No, Audrey.
No! I'm not losing you.
Are we down there?
Another version of us?
I don't know.
All those people, Mom,
we have to warn them.
There's no time.
They'll never believe us.
I need you to stay here
with your brother, okay?
Promise me. Do as I ask, okay?
- Okay, Mom.
- Okay? Stay there.
Stay there!
One-four-nine-two. Okay, okay.
Mom, who did you call?
Please, Audrey, just trust me.
How many more minutes
before it disappears?
Soon.
Why won't you tell me what's going on?
Listen.
What is it?
Mom, is that...
- It's Dad!
- Dad!
- Greg!
Denise?
What are you guys doing here?
What is this?
We're so happy to see you.
I thought you'd be mad at me
for doing deliveries.
- No. No.
- Dad.
Whatever you needed to do.
It doesn't matter.
I love you.
- We love you, Dad.
- I love you so much.
I love you too, but why are you here?
What's going on?
I know we've been having problems,
but, Greg, I never want
to be anywhere else
but here with you.
You do? Really?
Yes.
There's so much I have to tell you.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is happening?
Is that a fucking dinosaur?
Yeah, Dad.
Uh-huh.
It is.
♪ Leave a message
With the rain ♪
- Yeah. I told you!
- I don't think so.
♪ You can find me
Where the wind blows... ♪
♪ ...Good to the last
Decaffeinated drop ♪
♪ Maxwell House
Decaffeinated ♪
♪ Maxwell House ♪
♪ Delicious ♪
It was exactly two years ago today
that the neighborhood
of Flowervale disappeared
in the middle of the night,
replaced by a two-mile circle
of prehistoric forest.
Scientists and the U.S. military
contained the area,
capturing or killing dozens
of prehistoric animals.
Many of the survivors
owe their lives to the actions
taken by Flowervale resident Denise Platt
at that now-famous hillside phone booth.
Denise called me, collect,
and begged me to get in the car
and go straight to the hillside.
Thank God I did what she asked.
My husband thought she was crazy
calling in the middle of the night,
but there was something about her voice
that made me listen.
I have a lot of respect for Denise Platt.
We didn't always get along,
but hell,
she saved my life.
To this day, the cause
of the event is unknown,
though there's increasing speculation
about naturally occurring wormholes
with the ability to swap matter
between the present and the past.
Mom, dinner's ready
if you want to come eat.
Dad made barbecue.
Okay. Be right down.
Okay.
Good boy.
Hey!